let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What type of heating is at 368 La Montagna Strada?",
        answer: "Gas Forced Air",
        options: [
            "Gas Forced Air",
            "Electric Baseboard",
            "Gas Boiler",
            "Electric Ceiling Cable"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Who owns the property at 445 McKinley Ave?",
        answer: "David A. Hubbard",
        options: [
            "Dannis Adamson",
            "Five Star Property Management",
            "David A. Hubbard",
            "Juice Jar LLC",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "How many properties do we managage on Alamo St.?",
        answer: "3",
        options: [
            "4",
            "3",
            "12",
            "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following amenties are listed at 1011 Deon #1",
        answer: "None of the Above",
        options: [
            "Fenced Yard",
            "Fiber Optic Internet",
            "Deck",
            "None of the Above",
        ]
    }, 
    {
        numb: 5,
        question : "How many upstairs Aparment do we manage?",
        answer: "95",
        options: [
            "54",
            "95",
            "236",
            "10",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question : "Who was the turn coordinator to turn 482 C Pheasant Ridge?",
        answer: "Trent",
        options: [
            "Brett",
            "Chris",
            "Kevin",
            "Trent",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question : "What type of dwelling is 1205 N Main St?",
        answer: "Single Family Home",
        options: [
            "Single Family Home",
            "Multi Family Home",
            "Student Housing",
            "Townhome",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question : "What is the square footage of 590 W Maple?",
        answer: "2,418",
        options: [
            "2,043",
            "900",
            "2,311",
            "3,213",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question : "Who is the owner of 724 S 19th Ave?",
        answer: "Jason Christensen",
        options: [
            "Jason Christensen",
            "Stash Investments LLC",
            "Jay Christensen",
            "David Hubbard",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question : "Who was the resident at 1981 Bengalview Drive in January of 2023?",
        answer: "None of the Above",
        options: [
            "Jessica Hope",
            "James Wilske",
            "Bill Quale",
            "None of the Above",
        ]
    }
];